<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Terminology on</title><link>/docs/terminology/</link><description>Recent content in Terminology on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/terminology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Access token</title><link>/docs/terminology/access-token/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/terminology/access-token/</guid><description>When a visitor solves the CAPTCHA and sends their solution to an mCaptcha instance, the solution will be verified for correctness. If the solution is correct, mCaptcha will return a single use access token.
This access token should be attached to the visitor&amp;rsquo;s requited to the protected service and the protected service should validity of the access token with the mCaptcha instance and only allow access to protected resource if the access token is valid.</description></item><item><title>Cooldown Period</title><link>/docs/terminology/cooldown-period/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/terminology/cooldown-period/</guid><description>mCaptcha implements leaky bucket algorithm to measure current traffic levels. Cooldown period specifies the leak or the time after which a visitor addition is decremented.
For instance, if initial traffic level is 0 and a user visits one second later, the traffic level will be incremented to 1. Now, if the cooldown period is set to 30 seconds, the traffic level will be decremented after 30 seconds. So after 30 seconds, the traffic level will go from 1 to 0.</description></item><item><title>Difficulty Factor</title><link>/docs/terminology/difficulty-factor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/terminology/difficulty-factor/</guid><description>Difficulty factor determines the time it takes to solve a CAPTCHA. The higher the difficulty factor, the longer it will take to generate a proof of work for it to solve the CAPTCHA.
mCaptcha&amp;rsquo;s proof of work based mechanism makes it highly accessible to people with special needs but it is important to choose the difficulty factor with care as very high difficulty factors will make the CAPTCHA inaccessible to users on slow devices.</description></item><item><title>Site key</title><link>/docs/terminology/sitekey/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/terminology/sitekey/</guid><description>Site key is a unique identifier associated with CAPTCHA configurations created on mCaptcha. It is required to integrate a CAPTCHA with your website.
How to get site key? Go to &amp;ldquo;Site keys&amp;rdquo; on the side panel in the dashboard click on the clipboard button to copy the site key to your clipboard.</description></item><item><title>Visitor Threshold</title><link>/docs/terminology/visitor-threshold/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/terminology/visitor-threshold/</guid><description>mCaptcha&amp;rsquo;s variable difficulty factor mechanism requires a website&amp;rsquo;s traffic statistics be split into levels, so that it can deploy the right difficulty factor for each level.
Visitor threshold is used to traffic into levels and mCaptcha accepts a difficulty configuration for each of these levels. When current traffic exceeds a difficulty factor, mCaptcha will increase the difficulty factor to the next configured level.
For instance, consider the configuration given below:</description></item></channel></rss>