<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Defend Like Castles on</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in Defend Like Castles on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>mCaptcha is a kickass CAPTCHA systems that gives (DDoS) attackers a run for their money. And we do all of this without tracking your users. Oh and did I mention our UX is great?
At mCaptcha, we believe in digital freedom and privacy and so we built an proof-of-work based CAPTCHA system that doesn’t track. Seriously, no tracking. But that isn’t the killer feature, our system doesn’t require the user to pick cars or ID sidewalks — our system does it’s thing(usually at the click of a button) and gets out of the way.</description></item><item><title>Donate</title><link>/donate/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/donate/</guid><description>mCaptcha is a small operation that is self-funded. At the time of writing, we are not backed by any venture capitals. If you like mCaptcha, please consider donating. Your donations will go a long way in supporting us.
Some of the payment options are anonymous. You can optionally send me(@realaravinth) an email so that I can thank you :)
XMR 85QAHsHqg4WfA6G7ycXc7U4LmrSLCQARv6H9p3AYjf8o8YP WH3ngC8Zi7bUYGUifdXb54Xuz41kcu2pqgGFuAYp3VSh5JsR Monero address QR code Liberapay</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/privacy-policy/</guid><description>TLDR: We do not use cookies, we do not collect any personal data and logs aren&amp;rsquo;t shared with third-parties.
Website visitors No personal information is collected. No information is stored in the browser. No information is shared with, sent to or sold to third-parties. No information is shared with advertising companies. No information is mined and harvested for personal and behavioral trends. No information is monetized. Information we collect and what we use it for Website activity is logged and stored for a period of one month for debugging purposes.</description></item><item><title>Community</title><link>/community/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/community/</guid><description>Matrix Community Come say hi at our Matrix community!
Fediverse handle We are on the Fediverse at @mCapthca@batsense.net, toot at us for queries and whatnot :)
Official Twitter handle The project also has a twitter twitter presence at @m_captcha(Nitter hyperlink). This space is used in addition to the blog to post short updates.
Lead developer email Write to me at realaravinth@batsense.net!
Bug reports We use GitHub for managing tickets</description></item><item><title>Security</title><link>/security/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/security/</guid><description>Security is at the heart of mCaptcha. If you find any discrepancies in our software(see listing on our GitHub, services available)
Rules: Before you start Check the list of domains that are in scope for security research and the list of targets for useful information for getting started.
Check the list of bugs that have been classified as ineligible.
Check our changelog(in our GitHub repositories) for recently launched features.</description></item><item><title>Thanks</title><link>/thanks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/thanks/</guid><description>Free software libraries and tools mCaptcha is built entirely using free software libraries tools. We are grateful for all maintainers and contributors for their time and effort in making them!
Creative Commons licensed artwork mCaptcha shied logo is derived from this photo captured by Paweł Czerwiński. You can check out their work at:
Unsplash Instagram</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 19:23:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description>Matrix Community We have a Matrix community, come say hi!.
Lead developer You can find me(@realaravinth) on the Matrix, on GitHub or email me at realaravinth@batense.net.</description></item><item><title>Blog</title><link>/blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/</guid><description/></item><item><title>mCaptcha</title><link>/docs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Support</title><link>/support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/support/</guid><description>Commercial support is available from the lead developer, @realaravinth. To seek support, kindly contact:
Aravinth Manivannan
Email: support@mcaptcha.io
Phone: +91 99438 15996
8/1, Palaniappa Nagar, Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu, India - 641 041</description></item><item><title>Terms of Service</title><link>/tos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tos/</guid><description>All applications and infrastructure software used in mCaptcha are published under a Free Software license.
Support Please see here for support information.
Security Please see here for security information.
GDPR compliance Please see here for GDPR compliance.
No Questions Asked Cancellation and Refund Policy Full refund of purchases available for up to 15 days from the date of purchase. There is no capping on the refund amount. 100% of your purchase value would be refunded to you.</description></item></channel></rss>