<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Aravinth Manivannan on</title><link>/contributors/aravinth-manivannan/</link><description>Recent content in Aravinth Manivannan on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/contributors/aravinth-manivannan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Survey</title><link>/blog/survey/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/survey/</guid><description>Survey link: https://survey.mcaptcha.org/survey/campaigns/b717e51e-24d4-4ab6-912f-de2dfe3ce1fe/about
NOTE: The survey(at least, the lucky draw is temporarily suspended due to some logistical reasons. Apologies for any inconvenience caused.
mCaptcha relies on a proof-of-work(PoW) mechanism to guard against bots. In order for this to be effective, the difficulty factor should be configured properly. If the difficulty factor is too high all the time, it will inconvenience the users and if it&amp;rsquo;s too low during attack, the defence will be weak.</description></item><item><title>PoW performance</title><link>/blog/pow-performance/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/pow-performance/</guid><description>mCaptcha uses a proof-of-work(PoW) mechanism to rate limit users or potential bots. In order for this to be effective, the PoW should be configured properly. The difficulty requirement can&amp;rsquo;t be too high, as it could cause accessibility issues on the client-side while at the same time, it shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be too low, as it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t offer proper protection against bots.
Malicious bots(the ones that wreak havoc), run native code which is capable of running in a multi-threaded context.</description></item><item><title>Say hello to mCaptcha</title><link>/blog/say-hello-to-mcaptcha/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/say-hello-to-mcaptcha/</guid><description>At mCaptcha, we believe in digital freedom and privacy and so we built a proof-of-work based CAPTCHA system that doesn&amp;rsquo;t track. Seriously, no tracking. But that isn&amp;rsquo;t the killer feature, our system doesn&amp;rsquo;t require the user to pick cars or ID sidewalks &amp;mdash; our system does it&amp;rsquo;s thing(usually at the click of a button) and gets out of the way.
How does it work? mCaptcha uses SHA256 based proof-of-work(PoW) to rate limit users.</description></item></channel></rss>